{"message": "Successfully uploaded", "questions": [{"explanation": "mouse is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Select appropiate Singular or mass Noun from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the _____________ being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["zoo", "tree", "wagon", "mouse"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: in", "question": "In the following sentence identify Preposition or subordinating conjunction.", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["search", "in", "a", "went"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: of", "question": "In the following sentence identify Preposition or subordinating conjunction.", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["search", "of", "him", "a"]}, {"explanation": "in is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Select appropiate Preposition or subordinating conjunction from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "After that they went _____________ search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["in", "after", "by", "of"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: being", "question": "In the following sentence identify Verb (present participle).", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["being", "to", "idea", "lifted"]}, {"explanation": "tree is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Select appropiate Singular or mass Noun from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a _____________ .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["tree", "wagon", "lion", "paw"]}, {"explanation": "tied is Verb (past tense)", "question": "Select appropiate Verb (past tense) from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and _____________ him to a tree .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["was", "tied", "went", "lifted"]}, {"explanation": "that is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Select appropiate Preposition or subordinating conjunction from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him _____________ he lifted his paw and let him go .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["by", "in", "after", "that"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: a", "question": "In the following sentence identify Determiner.", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["to", "a", "few", "tree"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: the", "question": "In the following sentence identify Determiner.", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["lion", "captured", "to", "the"]}, {"explanation": "lion is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Select appropiate Singular or mass Noun from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The _____________ was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["search", "lion", "zoo", "wagon"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: to", "question": "In the following sentence identify to.", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["take", "to", "a", "that"]}, {"explanation": "lifted is Verb (past tense)", "question": "Select appropiate Verb (past tense) from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he _____________ his paw and let him go .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["tied", "lifted", "went", "was"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: the", "question": "In the following sentence identify Determiner.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["the", "was", "him", "let"]}, {"explanation": "search is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Select appropiate Singular or mass Noun from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "After that they went in _____________ of a wagon , to take him to the zoo .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["paw", "mouse", "search", "zoo"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: zoo", "question": "In the following sentence identify Singular or mass Noun.", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["a", "to", "in", "zoo"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: that", "question": "In the following sentence identify Preposition or subordinating conjunction.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["him", "that", "lifted", "tickled"]}, {"explanation": "wagon is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Select appropiate Singular or mass Noun from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "After that they went in search of a _____________ , to take him to the zoo .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["wagon", "search", "paw", "lion"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: tree", "question": "In the following sentence identify Singular or mass Noun.", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["to", "a", "tied", "tree"]}, {"explanation": "After is Preposition or subordinating conjunction", "question": "Select appropiate Preposition or subordinating conjunction from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": " _____________ that they went in search of a wagon , to take him to the zoo .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["After", "that", "in", "after"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: tied", "question": "In the following sentence identify Verb (past tense).", "comprehension": "Sometime later , a few hunters captured the lion , and tied him to a tree . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["tree", "tied", "a", "later"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: the", "question": "In the following sentence identify Determiner.", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["the", "was", "and", "lifted"]}, {"explanation": "Answer: was", "question": "In the following sentence identify Verb (past tense).", "comprehension": "The lion was so tickled by the idea of the mouse being able to help him that he lifted his paw and let him go . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["tickled", "The", "able", "was"]}], "success": 1}